MINJI KIM

124 Charlton Blvd, Toronto ON, M2R 2J1

Phone (416) 821-3591

Email dalimanju15@gmail.com

LinkedIn www.linkedin.com/in/mkim9713

Profile https://minjikim123.github.io/mk-portfolio/

An experienced programmer with dynamic work experiences in software development specializing in C# and .NET. with strong knowledge of SDLC and wide range of skill sets in object-oriented programming. Effective in both team and individual work environments, communicative, quick learner, and a talented problem solver.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Web application development -Node.js, React.js, ASP.NET, HTML, CSS
- WPF development C#, .NET
- Data Management SQL, PL/SQL, NoSQL
- Java
- RPA (Robotic Process Automation) Selenium, BluePrism

EXPERIENCE

2020-10 – 2020-12	Peer Tutor
	Centennial College, Toronto, ON
	• Tutored 20+ students on technical skills: Java EE, C# (WPF), and Web development (MERN stack)
2020-05 – 2020-08	Software Developer Intern
	Zenith I&T, Seoul, Korea
	 Successfully implemented RPA processes for the application of auto-execution on a remote production server using tools such as: Microsoft Automation API, PsTools, and SQL.
	 Facilitated daily data export jobs by creating a web automation tool using Selenium, C#, and XML.
2019-09 – 2020-12	Software Developer Co-op
	RBC, Toronto, ON
	 Utilized Blue Prism RPA processes, .NET, Selenium, and SQL to develop an automation tool for ServiceNow incident ticketing process of 5+ different client applications.
	 Assisted in creating an efficient C# tool to manage data from Active Directory by extracting and exporting the data to excel.
2019-01 – 2019-04	Application Developer Co-op
	CIBC, Toronto, ON
	• Supported in developing a user-friendly WPF tool to run calculation jobs and managed database-level user roles and privileges on different servers.
	 Automated the daily execution of 10+ batch files to manage mortgage processes and to generate reports.
EDUCATION	

2017-09 - 2020-12 **Software Engineering Technology Advanced Diploma** (Honours)

Centennial College, Toronto, ON

PROJECT

EduCloud - MERN (MongoDB, Express.js, React.js, Node.js) Stack, REST API, WebSocket

https://github.com/MinJiKim123/mk-mern-project

Created a website in which students can communicate through chat function and schedule events via calendar

Movie4Share - ASP.NET, MVC Pattern, AWS S3, AWS DynamoDB, AWS Elastic Beanstalk

https://github.com/MinJiKim123/mk-aspnet-aws-uploadvideo

Developed and published an interactive website that lets users to upload and download videos with reviews